Perimeter of a Square =P=4 x a
Where a = Length of the sides of a Square                   

Perimeter of a Rectangle=P=2(l+b)
Where, l = Length ; b = Breadth

Area of a Square=A=a^2
Where a = Length of the sides of a Square

Area of a Rectangle=A=l × b
Where, l = Length ; b = Breadth

Area of a Triangle=A=b×h2
Where, b = base of the triangle ; h = height of the triangle

Area of a Trapezoid=A=(b1+b2)h2
Where, b1 & b2 are the bases of the Trapezoid ; h = height of the Trapezoid

Area of a Circle=A=π×r^2
Circumference of a Circle=A=2 x π x r
Where, r = Radius of the Circle

Surface Area of a Cube=S=6 x a^2
Where, a = Length of the sides of a Cube


Surface Area of a Cylinder=S=2 x π x r x h
Volume of a Cylinder=V=π x r^2 x h
Where, r = Radius of the base of the Cylinder ; 
h = Height of the Cylinder

Surface Area of a Cone=S=πr(r+h2+r2−−−−−−√)
Volume of a Cone=V=π x r^2 x h
Where, r = Radius of the base of the Cone, h = Height of the Cone

Surface Area of a Sphere=S=4 x π x r^2
Volume of a Sphere=V=4/3 x π x r^3
Where, r = Radius of the Sphere                                                                           
Degree <-> Radian

double radian,degree;
/* Convert radiun to degree */
radian=1.047198 ;
degree=(radian*360)/(2*M_PI);
pf("The radian = %lf is %lf degree\n",radian,degree);
    
/* Convert radian to degree */
degree=60 ;
radian=(degree*2*M_PI)/360;
pf("The degree = %lf is %lf radian\n",degree,radian);